<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<root>
  <title>CEE Virtual Laboratory</title>
  <titletext>Welcome to the virtual laboratory of the Center of Experimental Economics at the University of Copenhagen.
    &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To log on please use the username and password provided to you. 
    After successfully&lt;br/&gt;logging on to the experiment, please follow the instructions.</titletext>
  <paymentvar>payment</paymentvar>
  
  <screens>
    
<!-- General Intro for both Players -->
    <screen wait="true">
      <message text="&lt;b&gt; Welcome to this experiment! &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 
      
    	This experiment is part of a research project undertaken by researchers from the University of Copenhagen and Université 
	Libre de Bruxelles.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
	
    	By participating in this experiment you can earn money. The amount of money you can earn will depend on your decisions, 
	but might also depend on the decisions of another person.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;          
    
    	More precisely, the experiment consists of two different stages and a questionnaire. 
    	The amount of money you can earn in Stage 1 will only depend on your decisions. Your earnings in Stage 2 will depend on your decisions, 
    	but might also depend on those of another player. At the end of the experiment the computer will 
   	randomly choose a stage and pay you according to your earnings in that stage.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
    
    	The experiment is anonymous: you will neither learn the identity of the person that you are paired with in Stage 2 
    	nor will the person that you are paired with learn your identity.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 
    
    	During this experiment you and the person that you are paired with will be randomly assigned to one of two different roles. 
    	We name these roles 'Person A' and 'Person B'. This means that during this experiment you will be either Person A or Person B. 
    	If you are Person A, the person that you are paired with is Person B and vice versa.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
    
    	On the following screens you will receive explanations which describe the nature of the decision situations you will be confronted 
    	with (i.e. which decisions can be taken and what their consequences are).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
    
    	In general, the experiment will proceed as follows: You will receive instructions explaining the first stage. 
	You will then be asked to answer control questions to make sure you understood the decision situation you’ll find 
	yourself in. Subsequently, you will go through Stage 1 of the experiment. The second stage will then follow the same 
	procedure. Finally, you will answer a short questionnaire to finish the experiment. We will then proceed with the payments."/>
    </screen>
 

<!-- General Instructions regarding the box-clicking task for both Players-->
    <screen backbutton="true">
        <message text="&lt;b/&gt;Stage 1: Instructions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
				
	Remember the experiment consists of two different stages and a questionnaire. At the top of the screen you will always find information about
	your progress, indicating in which stage you currently are.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

	In Stage 1 you can decide how many boxes you want to click away in a box-clicking task.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 

	The task consists of a series of &lt;b/&gt; screens &lt;/b&gt; with black boxes. When you click on a black box it disappears. 
	After some seconds the whole screen disappears together with the remaining boxes and a new screen with new black boxes comes up. 
        Your performance on the task is measured by the percentage of black boxes you click away. 
	It is between 0% (you do not click away any black box) and 100% (you click away all black boxes that appear on each screen).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

	Press 'Next' at the bottom of this page in order to get to a trial round where you can familiarize yourself with the clicking task.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
	After finishing the trial round, you will learn how this task affects your earnings in Stage 1. 
	For now, you only need to know that your expected earnings from the actual task grow with each box you click away.
	Hence, the more boxes you click away in the actual task, the more you can expect to earn in Stage 1."/>
    </screen>
    
    
<!-- Practice Round for both Players-->
    <screen condition="#[ Self.Role == 1 ]#" noreload="true">
      <question var="boxdata" javascript="TaskBrowse.js" javascriptinput=""/>
      <question var="score1" javascriptinput="-1000"/>
      <question var="browse" javascriptinput="9999"/>
    </screen>

    <screen condition="#[ Self.Role == 2 ]#" noreload="true">
      <question text="&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;" var="boxdata" javascript="TaskBrowse.js" javascriptinput=""/>
      <question var="score1" javascriptinput="-1000"/>
      <question var="browse" javascriptinput="9999"/>
    </screen>
    
    
<!-- Explanation of Payment Function for both Players in Stage 1-->
    <screen backbutton="false">

        <message text="&lt;b/&gt; Stage 1: Instructions &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;        
            
	You have just finished a short trial round and familiarized yourself with the task. Your performance in 
	the trial round (i.e. the percentage of boxes you just clicked away) does not affect your final earnings 
	in any way. However, the actual task, which you will go through in Stage 1 and which consists of more screens, 
	might be relevant for your earnings. Remember, the experiment consists of two stages and one of these stages 
	will randomly be chosen at the end of the experiment and paid out. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

	&lt;b/&gt;What are your earnings in Stage 1?&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
            
	Your payoff in Stage 1 is &lt;b&gt; performance-based &lt;b/&gt;. That is, your earnings in this stage depend 
	on the percentage of boxes you clicked away. At the end of the actual task you will be informed about the 
	percentage of boxes that you clicked away in Stage 1.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
            
	You can either earn 150 DKK or 225 DKK in Stage 1. The likelihood with which you earn 225 DKK is given by the 
	percentage of boxes you clicked away. The more boxes you click away and thus, the higher the percentage of 
	boxes you clicked away during the box-clicking task, the more likely it is that you earn 225 DKK in Stage 1 
	of this experiment. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
                              
	&lt;b/&gt;Examples&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
	
	If you click away 30% of the boxes, you will have a 30% chance to earn 225 DKK in Stage 1 and a 70% 
	chance to earn 150 DKK. If you click away 55% of the boxes that appear during the clicking task, you 
	will have a 55% chance to earn 225 DKK and a 45% chance to earn 150 DKK. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

            
	On the next page we will ask you control questions to make sure that you understood the explanations so far. 
	Upon answering these questions correctly you can proceed with the box-clicking task of Stage 1. "/>
    </screen>
    

<!-- First Set of Control Questions for both Players-->
    <screen backbutton="true">
        <question text="&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b/&gt;Stage 1: Control questions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
            &lt;b/&gt;Question 1&lt;/b&gt;: Remember, in Stage 1 your performance will determine the likelihood with 
	    which you earn 225 DKK. Imagine you click away 75% of the boxes, what is the likelihood with which you 
	    earn &lt;b/&gt;225 DKK&lt;/b&gt; in this stage?&lt;br/&gt; 
            Please answer by choosing a number between 0 and 100 where 0 means 0%, 2 means 2% etc.&lt;br/&gt;"
        var="Control1.1" defaultinput="#[ Self.Answers['control1'] if 'control1' in Self.Answers else '' ]#" textbox="true" number="int" min="75" max="75" />

        <question text="&lt;b/&gt;Question 2&lt;/b&gt;: Imagine you click away 50% of the boxes, what is the likelihood with
	    which you earn &lt;b/&gt;225 DKK&lt;/b&gt; in this stage?&lt;br/&gt; 
            Please answer by choosing a number between 0 and 100 where 0 means 0%, 2 means 2% etc.&lt;br/&gt;"
        var="Control1.2" defaultinput="#[ Self.Answers['control3'] if 'control3' in Self.Answers else '' ]#" textbox="true" number="int" min="50" max="50" />

        <question text="&lt;b/&gt;Question 3&lt;/b&gt;: Imagine you click away 25% of the boxes, what is the likelihood with
	    which you earn &lt;b/&gt;150 DKK&lt;/b&gt; in this stage?&lt;br/&gt; 
            Please answer by choosing a number between 0 and 100 where 0 means 0%, 2 means 2% etc.&lt;br/&gt;"
        var="Control1.3" defaultinput="#[ Self.Answers['control3'] if 'control3' in Self.Answers else '' ]#" textbox="true" number="int" min="75" max="75" />
    </screen>
    

<!-- Stage 1: Box-Clicking Task for both Players-->
    <screen wait="true" condition="#[ Self.Role == 1 ]#">
        <message text="&lt;b/&gt; Stage 1: Box-clicking task &lt;b/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;/br&gt;
            Remember, your earnings in Stage 1 will depend on your own performance."/>
        <message text="On the next page the work task will start. Press 'Next' when you are ready."/>
    </screen>

    <screen wait="true" condition="#[ Self.Role == 2 ]#">
      <message text="&lt;b/&gt; Stage 1: Box-clicking task &lt;b/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;/br&gt;
            Remember, your earnings in Stage 1 will depend on your own performance."/>
      <message text="On the next page the work task will start. Press 'Next' when you are ready."/>
    </screen>

    <screen noreload="true">
        <question var="boxdata" javascript="TaskBrowse.js" javascriptinput=""/>
        <question var="score2" javascriptinput="1"/>
        <question var="browse" javascriptinput="9999"/>
    </screen>
    
    
<!-- Stage 1: Both Players learn their Performance-->
    <screen wait="false" >
        <message text="&lt;b/&gt; Stage 1: Results &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
            Your performance: You clicked away #[ Self.Answers['score2'] ]#% of the boxes during the box-clicking task 
	    in Stage 1. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
            This means you have a #[ Self.Answers['score2'] ]#% chance to earn 225 DKK in Stage 1 and a 
	    #[ 100 - (float(Self.Answers['score2'])) ]#% chance to earn 150 DKK.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 
               
            Remember, at the end of the experiment the computer will randomly choose a stage, determine your earnings 
	    in this stage and pay you accordingly." />
	    
        <message text="Please press 'Next' to start Stage 2 of the experiment." />
    </screen>
    
    
<!--Players Learn their Type-->
    <screen backbutton="false" condition="#[ Self.Role == 1 ]#">
        <message text="&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b/&gt;Stage 2: Instructions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
          
            You just finished Stage 1 of this experiment. You will now learn which role you are assigned to 
            in Stage 2 and proceed with Stage 2.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
          
            &lt;b/&gt;Your Role&lt;/b&gt;: You are &lt;b/&gt;Person B&lt;/b&gt;. 
            In this stage, you will be paired with another person, Person A.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
            
            The next pages will give you detailed instructions for Stage 2. 
            Please read them carefully and raise your hand if you have any questions."/>
    </screen>

    <screen backbutton="false" condition="#[ Self.Role == 2 ]#">
      <message text="&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b/&gt;Stage 2: Instructions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
          
            You just finished Stage 1 of this experiment. You will now learn which role you are assigned to 
            in Stage 2 and proceed with Stage 2.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
          
            &lt;b/&gt;Your Role&lt;/b&gt;: You are &lt;b/&gt;Person A&lt;/b&gt;. 
            In this stage, you will be paired with another person, Person B.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
            
            The next pages will give you detailed instructions for Stage 2. 
            Please read them carefully and raise your hand if you have any questions."/>
    </screen>
    
    
<!-- Instructions Stage 2 Role 1/B-->
    <screen backbutton="true" condition="#[ Self.Role == 1 ]#">
        <message text="
	&lt;b/&gt; Stage 2: Instructions &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;
          
	&lt;b/&gt; Remember &lt;/b&gt;: You are Person B and you are paired with another person, Person A, 
	in Stage 2. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;
               
	In Stage 2 you are paired with another person, Person A. You will be confronted 
	with the same box-clicking task as in Stage 1. The difficulty of the task is exactly the same as before. 
	&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        
	This stage, however, is different from the first stage. Person A 
	will not work on the task again. Your performance will generate income for Person A and she will pay you 
	for your work on the task from her income. Another difference is that the payoff you will 
	receive from Person A will either be random or performance-based. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
	
	The next pages will explain, what 'random' as well as 'performance-based' means and how this affects the earnings
	of you and the person you are paired with in this stage."/>
    </screen>
		       
                              
    <screen backbutton="true" condition="#[ Self.Role == 1 ]#">
        <message text="
	&lt;b/&gt; Stage 2: Instructions &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;
          
	&lt;b/&gt; Remember &lt;/b&gt;: You are Person B and you are paired with another person, Person A, 
	in Stage 2. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;
		       
	A ‘random’ payoff simply means that you have a 50% chance to earn 150 DKK and a 50% chance to earn 225 DKK. 
	The random payoff is like a flip of a coin which decides whether you get 225 DKK or 150 DKK.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  
	
	A ‘performance-based’ payoff means that your payoff is determined as in Stage 1. That is, the likelihood with 
	which you earn 225 DKK is given by the percentage of boxes you clicked away in Stage 2. The higher the 
	percentage of boxes you clicked away during the box-clicking task, the more likely it is that you earn 225 DKK."/>
    </screen>
		       
                              
    <screen backbutton="true" condition="#[ Self.Role == 1 ]#">
        <message text="
	&lt;b/&gt; Stage 2: Instructions &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;
          
	&lt;b/&gt; Remember &lt;/b&gt;: You are Person B and you are paired with another person, Person A, 
	in Stage 2. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;
               
	Whether you will receive a random payoff or a performance-based payoff depends on Person A (the person you 
	are paired with). More precisely, Person A will be informed about the percentage of boxes you clicked away in 
	Stage 1 and then chooses between two options. The two options a) and b) that Person A can choose between are 
	as follows: &lt;br/&gt; 
		       
		       &lt;ol type=&quot;a&quot;&gt;
		       &lt;li&gt; with a 75%  chance your earnings in stage 2 will be performance-based and with a 25% 
		       chance your earnings will be random. &lt;/li&gt;
		       &lt;li&gt; with a 25% chance your earnings in stage 2 will be performance-based and with a 75% 
		       chance your earnings will be random. &lt;/li&gt;
		       &lt;/ol&gt; 
               
	In a nutshell, if Person A chooses option a), i.e. the higher likelihood of a performance-based pay, it is
	more likely that your payoff in Stage 2 will depend on your performance in the clicking task. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 
	               
	You will be informed about Person A’s choice before you decide how many boxes you want to click away in the 
	box-clicking task in Stage 2. However, neither you nor Person A will be informed about whether your payoff 
	will actually be random or performance-based. You will only be informed about the choice of Person A, i.e. 
	the likelihood with which your earnings in Stage 2 will depend on your performance. "/>
    </screen>
		       
                              
    <screen backbutton="true" condition="#[ Self.Role == 1 ]#">
        <message text="
	&lt;b/&gt; Stage 2: Instructions &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;
          
	&lt;b/&gt; Remember &lt;/b&gt;: You are Person B and you are paired with another person, Person A, 
	in Stage 2. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;

	Following this, you have to make a decision on how much effort to put into the box-clicking task in Stage 2. 
	Importantly, you will make this decision in two steps: First, you can choose your workload. That is, you can 
	choose the number of screens you intend to work on. You can thereby choose any number between 0 and 25 where 
	25 is the number of screens you also encountered in Stage 1. In the second step, the box-clicking task will 
	start with the number of screens you have chosen and you can decide, as in Stage 1, how many boxes you want 
	to click away. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;
               
	Note that your performance is measured as the percentage of boxes you clicked away out of all boxes you could 
	have clicked away on all 25 screens. If you decided, for example, to work on 20 screens (which is 80% of the 
	total number of screens), your performance cannot be higher than 80% even if you click on every box that is 
	displayed. You must also know that the time a screen is displayed is not affected by your choice. As a 
	consequence, the difficulty of the task remains the same, since you have as much time per screen as before."/>
    </screen>
    
    <screen backbutton="true" condition="#[ Self.Role == 1 ]#">
      
      <message text="
	&lt;b/&gt; Stage 2: Instructions &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;
          
	&lt;b/&gt; Remember &lt;/b&gt;: You are Person B and you are paired with another person, Person A, 
	in Stage 2. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;

	&lt;b/&gt; What are your and Person A's payoffs in this stage? &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 
               
	Person A’s earnings in Stage 2 have several components. First, Person A’s choice regarding the likelihood 
	with which your payoff is performance-based is connected to a cost that Person A has to pay. Specifically, 
	Person A’s costs are as follows. If Person A decides that the likelihood with which your payoff in Stage 2 
	is performance-based is 25%, she has to pay 20 DKK. If Person A decides that the likelihood with which your 
	payoff in Stage 2 is performance-based is 75%, she has to pay 25 DKK. In addition to these costs, Person A 
	pays your earnings but also receives the profit generated from your work on the task in Stage 2. Specifically,
	her earnings are as follows. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
               
	Person A's earnings = 350 + 0.75 * Percentage of boxes you clicked away - Your payoff - Person A's costs &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
               
	&lt;b&gt; Your earnings in Stage 2 are: &lt;b/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;

	Your earnings = you will either receive a random or a performance-based payoff of 225 DKK or 150 DKK. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;
               
	&lt;b/&gt; Examples &lt;/b&gt; : &lt;br/&gt;

	Imagine Person A chooses a likelihood of 25% and your performance on the clicking task is that you clicked away 40% of the boxes.
	This means,&lt;br/&gt; 
	[1] with a 25% chance: your Stage 2 earnings are 225 DKK with 40% and 150 DKK with 60%.&lt;br/&gt;
	[2] with a 75% chance: your Stage 2 earnings are 225 DKK with 50% and 150 DKK with 50%.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
               
	Assume now that the random process determines that you receive 225 DKK from the work on the task in Stage 2. 
	Given this, Person A's earnings in Stage 2 are: &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;
               
	Person A's earnings = 350 + 0.75 * 40  - 225 - 5 = 135 DKK &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
                   
	On the next page, we will ask you and the Person you are paired with to answer control questions to make sure 
	that the instructions are clear. Upon answering these questions correctly, you can proceed with the second 
	stage of the experiment. "/>
    </screen>

    
<!-- Second Set of Control Questions, Role 1/B -->
    <screen backbutton="true"  condition="#[ Self.Role == 1 ]#">

      <question text="
	&lt;b/&gt; Stage 2: Control questions &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;
        
        To answer the following questions, you have to remember how your performance is measured and how the clicking 
	task looks like. You have seen that the task consists of a series of screens with black boxes; after a few 
	seconds the whole screen disappears together with the remaining boxes and a new screen with new black boxes 
	comes up. Below, you will be asked about the consequences of your workload decision. If you have problems 
	finding the correct answers, you can press the ‘Back’-button below and read the instructions once again. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
                
        Imagine you choose to work on half the number of screens &lt;b&gt; (number of screens) &lt;b/&gt;.
        What will your performance be if you manage to click away every box that is 
	displayed to you on these screens? &lt;br/&gt;
        Please answer by typing in a number between 0 and 100 where 0 means 0%, 3 means 3% etc. &lt;br/&gt;"
	var="Control2.1" defaultinput="Question 1" textbox="true" number="int" min="50" max="50"/>

       <question text="Imagine again you choose to work on half the number of screens (number of screens). 
	What will your performance be if you manage to click away every second box that is 
        displayed to you on these screens? &lt;br/&gt;
        Please answer by typing in a number between 0 and 100 where 0 means 0%, 3 means 3% etc. &lt;br/&gt;"
        var="Control2.2" defaultinput="Question 2" textbox="true" number="int" min="25" max="25"/>

      <question text="Imagine you clicked away 75% of the boxes on each screen in Stage 1. Remember that this would translate
        into a performance of 75%. Imagine further, that you expect to click the same amount of boxes per screen in Stage 2 and
        that you choose to work on 5 out of 25 screens (20% of the Screens), what would your performance in Stage 2 be in that case? &lt;br/&gt;
        Please answer by typing in a number between 0 and 100 where 0 means 0%, 3 means 3% etc. &lt;br/&gt;"
        var="Control2.3" defaultinput="Question 3" textbox="true" number="int" min="15" max="15"/>

    </screen>

    <screen backbutton="true"  condition="#[ Self.Role == 1 ]#">

      <question text="&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b/&gt;Stage 2: Control questions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
          
        Think about the differences between Stage 1 and Stage 2. Concerning your payoff, what is the major difference 
	between these two stages? &lt;br/&gt;
        Please read the following statements and choose the correct one by typing the corresponding number into the field below. &lt;br/&gt;
		      &lt;ol type=&quot;1&quot;&gt;
		      &lt;li&gt; The payment in Stage 1 was performance-based, in Stage 2 it is not. &lt;/li&gt;
		      &lt;li&gt; Person A can choose the likelihood with which I receive the higher payment. &lt;/li&gt;
		      &lt;li&gt; Instead of a 100% chance of receiving a performance-based payment, there now is 
		      only a 25% chance of receiving a performance-based payment in Stage 2. &lt;/li&gt; 
		      &lt;li&gt; Instead of a 100% chance of receiving a performance-based payment, Person A can now 
		      decide on the likelihood with which my payment is performance based. &lt;/li&gt;
		      &lt;/ol&gt; "
		
        var="Control2.4" defaultinput="Question 1" textbox="true" number="int" min="4" max="4"/>
      
      
       <question text="
	Assume you expect to click away less than 50% of the boxes in Stage 2. Given this, which of the two payment 
	mechanisms, i.e. random or performance-based, gives you a higher expected payoff? &lt;br/&gt;
	Please read the following statements and choose the correct one by typing the corresponding number into the 
	field below. &lt;br/&gt;
		       &lt;ol type=&quot;1&quot;&gt;
		       &lt;li&gt; The performance-based payoff gives me higher expected earnings in Stage 2. &lt;/li&gt;
		       &lt;li&gt; The random payoff gives me higher expected earnings in Stage 2. &lt;/li&gt;
		       &lt;li&gt;Both payoffs give me the same expected earnings in Stage 2. &lt;/li&gt;
		       &lt;/ol&gt; "
		 
         var="Control2.5" defaultinput="Question 2" textbox="true" number="int" min="2" max="2"/>

      <question text="
	Assume you expect to click away more than 50% of the boxes in Stage 2. Given this, which of the two payment 
	mechanisms, i.e. random or performance-based, gives you a higher expected payoff? &lt;br/&gt;
	Please read the following statements and choose the correct one by typing the corresponding number into the 
	field below. &lt;br/&gt;
		       &lt;ol type=&quot;1&quot;&gt;
		       &lt;li&gt; The performance-based payoff gives me higher expected earnings in Stage 2. &lt;/li&gt;
		       &lt;li&gt; The random payoff gives me higher expected earnings in Stage 2. &lt;/li&gt;
		       &lt;li&gt;Both payoffs give me the same expected earnings in Stage 2. &lt;/li&gt;
		       &lt;/ol&gt; "
		
         var="Control2.6" defaultinput="Question 3" textbox="true" number="int" min="1" max="1"/>


      <question text="
	Imagine you expect to click away 30% of the boxes. Do you receive a higher expected payoff if Person A chooses 
	a 25% or a 75% likelihood of you receiving a performance-based payoff? &lt;br/&gt;
	Please read the following statements and choose the correct one by typing the corresponding number into the 
	field below. &lt;br/&gt;
		      &lt;ol type=&quot;1&quot;&gt;
		      &lt;li&gt; 75%. &lt;/li&gt;
		      &lt;li&gt; Both yield the same expected payoff. &lt;/li&gt;
		      &lt;li&gt; 25%. &lt;/li&gt;
		      &lt;/ol&gt; " 
		
	var="Control2.7" defaultinput="Question 4" textbox="true" number="int" min="3" max="3"/>


       <question text="
	Imagine you expect to click away 60% of the boxes. Do you receive a higher expected payoff if Person A chooses 
	a 25% or a 75% likelihood of you receiving a performance-based payoff? &lt;br/&gt;
	Please read the following statements and choose the correct one by typing the corresponding number into the 
	field below. &lt;br/&gt;
		      &lt;ol type=&quot;1&quot;&gt;
		      &lt;li&gt; 75%. &lt;/li&gt;
		      &lt;li&gt; Both yield the same expected payoff. &lt;/li&gt;
		      &lt;li&gt; 25%. &lt;/li&gt;
		      &lt;/ol&gt; "
		 
	var="Control2.8" defaultinput="Question 5" textbox="true" number="int" min="1" max="1"/>

    </screen>

<!-- Instructions Stage 2 Role 2/A-->
    <screen backbutton="true" condition="#[ Self.Role == 2 ]#">
        <message text="
	&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b/&gt;Stage 2: Instructions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
          
	&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b/&gt;Remember&lt;/b&gt;: You are Person A.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
                 
	In Stage 2 you are paired with another person, Person B, who will be confronted 
	with the same box-clicking task as in Stage 1. The difficulty of the task is exactly the same as before.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
               
	In this stage Person B's (the Person that you are paired with) performance will generate income for you and
	you will pay his income for the work on the task.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
                              
	Specifically, Person B will either receive a random payoff unrelated to his work effort or a performance-based payoff.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;
				
	A random payoff simply means that he has a 50% chance to earn 75 DKK and a 50% chance to earn 125 DKK.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 
				
	A performance-based payoff means that his payoff is determined as in Stage 1. That is, the likelihood with which he earns 125 DKK 
	is given by the percentage of boxes he clicked away. The higher the percentage of boxes he clicked away during the box-clicking task,
	the more likely it is that he earns 125 DKK. Because you are paying him/her eventually, the probability with which Person B receives 
	125 DKK also affects your expected earnings from Stage 2.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
               
	Whether he will receive a random payoff or a performance-based payoff is influenced by you.  More precisely, you will be informed about
	the percentage of boxes Person B clicked away in Stage 1 before you have to choose the likelihood with which he receives a performance-based 
	payoff in Stage 2. 
	You can choose a likelihood of either 25% or 75% where 25% means that there is a 25% chance that Person B receives a performance-based payoff and 75% 
	means that there is a 75% chance that he receives a performance-based payoff.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 
               
	In a nutshell, the higher the likelihood that you choose, the more likely it is that his earnings, and therefore your earnings, 
	in Stage 2 will depend on his performance during the task in Stage 2.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 
               
	Person B will be informed about your choice before he decides how many boxes he wants to click away in the box-clicking task in Stage 2. 
	However, neither you nor Person B will be informed about whether his payoff will actually be random or performance-based. 
	Person A will only be informed about the likelihood chosen by you, i.e. the likelihood with which his earnings in Stage 2 will depend on 
	his performance.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
               
	Following this, Person B has to make a decision on how much effort to put into the box-clicking task in Stage 2. 
	Importantly, he will make this decision in two steps: First, he can choose his workload. That is, Person B can choose the number of 
	screens he intends to work on. He can thereby choose any number between 0 and 25 where 25 is the number of screens you also encountered 
	in Stage 1. In the second step, the box-clicking task will start with the number of screens he has chosen and he can decide, as in Stage 1, 
	how many boxes he wants to click away.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
               
	Note that Person B's performance is measured as the percentage of boxes he clicked away out of all boxes he could have clicked away on 
	all 25 screens. If Person B decided, for example, to work on 20 screens (which is 80% of the total number of screens), his performance cannot 
	be higher than 80% even if Person B clicks on every box that is displayed. You must also know that the time a screen is displayed is not affected 
	by his choice. As a consequence, the difficulty of the task remains the same, since he has as much time per screen as before."/>
    </screen>

    <screen backbutton="true" condition="#[ Self.Role == 2 ]#">

      <message text="
	&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b/&gt;Stage 2: Instructions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
          
	&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b/&gt;Remember&lt;/b&gt;: You are Person A.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

	&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b/&gt;What are your and Person A's payoffs in this stage?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  
               
	Your earnings in Stage 2 have several components. First, your choice
	regarding the likelihood with which Person B's payoff is performance-based is connected to a cost that you
	have to pay. Specifically, your costs are as follows. If you decide that the likelihood with 
	which Person B's payoff in Stage 2 is performance-based is 25%, you have to pay 5 DKK. 
	If you decide that the likelihood with which Person B's payoff in Stage 2 is performance-based is 75%, 
	you have to pay 30 DKK. In addition to these costs, you pay Person B's earnings but also receive the 
	profit generated from Person B's work on the task in Stage 2. Specifically, your earnings are as follows.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        
	Your earnings = 200 + 0.5 * Percentage of boxes you clicked away - Your payoff - Your costs&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
               
	Person B's earnings in Stage 2 are:&lt;br/&gt;  

	Person B's earnings = you will either receive a random or a performance-based payoff of 125 DKK or 75 DKK.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
               
	&lt;b/&gt;Examples&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br/&gt;

	Imagine you choose a likelihood of 25% and Person B's performance on the clicking task is that he clicked away 40% of the boxes.
	This means,&lt;br/&gt; 
	[1] with a 25% chance: Person B's Stage 2 earnings are 125 DKK with 40% and 75 DKK with 60%.&lt;br/&gt;
	[2] with a 75% chance: Person B's Stage 2 earnings are 125 DKK with 50% and 75 DKK with 50%.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
               
	Assume now that the random process determines that Person B receives 125 DKK from the work on the task in Stage 2. 
	Given this, your earnings in Stage 2 are:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
               
	Your earnings = 200 + 0.5 * 40  - 125 - 5 = 90 DKK &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
                   
	On the next page, we will ask you and the Person you are paired with to answer control questions 
	to make sure that the instructions are clear. 
	Upon answering these questions correctly, you can proceed with the second stage of the experiment."/>
    </screen>
    

<!-- Second Set of Control Questions, Role 2/A  -->
    <screen backbutton="true"  condition="#[ Self.Role == 2 ]#">

      <question text="&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b/&gt;Stage 2: Control questions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        
        To answer the following questions, you have to remember how your performance is measured and how the clicking task looks like. 
        You have seen that the task consists of a series of screens with black boxes; after some seconds the whole 
        screen disappears together with the remaining boxes and a new screen with new black boxes comes up.
        Below, you will be asked about the consequences of Person B's workload decision. To answer these questions, it is crucial that
        you understand how his  performance is measured. If you have problems finding the correct answers, you can press the
        'Back'-button below and read the instructions once again. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
                
        Imagine Person B chooses to work on half the number of screens (number of screens).
        What will his performance be if he manages to click away every box that is 
	displayed to him/her on these screens? &lt;br/&gt;
        Please answer by typing in a number between 0 and 100 where 0 means 0%, 3 means 3% etc. &lt;br/&gt;"
	var="Control2.1" defaultinput="" textbox="true" number="int" min="50" max="50"/>

      <question text="Imagine Person B chooses to work on half the number of screens (number of screens).
        What will his  performance be if he manages to click away every second box that is 
	displayed to him/her on these screens? &lt;br/&gt;
        Please answer by typing in a number between 0 and 100 where 0 means 0%, 3 means 3% etc. &lt;br/&gt;"
        var="Control2.2" defaultinput="" textbox="true" number="int" min="25" max="25"/>

      <question text="Imagine Person B clicked away 75% of the boxes on each screen in Stage 1. Remember that this would translate
        into a performance of 75%. Imagine further, that he expects to click the same amount of boxes per screen in Stage 2 and
        that he chooses to work on 5 out of 25 screens (20% of the Screens), what would Person B's performance in Stage 2 be in that case? &lt;br/&gt;
        Please answer by typing in a number between 0 and 100 where 0 means 0%, 3 means 3% etc. &lt;br/&gt;"
        var="Control2.3" defaultinput="" textbox="true" number="int" min="15" max="15"/>

    </screen>

    <screen backbutton="true"  condition="#[ Self.Role == 2 ]#">

      <question text="&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b/&gt;Stage 2: Control questions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
          
        Think about the differences between Stage 1 and Stage 2. 
	Considering Person B's payment resulting from that stage, what is a major difference? &lt;br/&gt;
        Please read the following statements and choose the correct one by typing the corresponding number into the field below. &lt;br/&gt;
        1) The payment in Stage 1 was performance-based, in Stage 2 it is not. &lt;br/&gt;
        2) I can choose the likelihood with which Person B receives the higher payment. &lt;br/&gt;
        3) Instead of a 100% chance of receiving a performance-based payment, there now is only a 25% 
	   chance of receiving a performance-based payoff in Stage 2. &lt;br/&gt;
        4) Instead of a 100% chance of receiving a performance-based payment,
	   I can now decide on the likelihood with which Person B's payoff is performance based. &lt;br/&gt;"
        var="Control2.4" defaultinput="" textbox="true" number="int" min="4" max="4"/>


      <question text="Assume Person B expects to click away less than 50% of the boxes in Stage 2. 
        Which of the following statements is true? &lt;br/&gt;
        Hint: In this experiment, we understand a payoff as the mechanism that determines your earnings in a given stage. &lt;br/&gt;
        Please read the following statements and choose the correct one by typing the corresponding number into the field below. &lt;br/&gt;
        1) The performance-based payoff gives him/her higher expected earnings in Stage 2. &lt;br/&gt;
        2) The random payoff gives him/her higher expected earnings in Stage 2. &lt;br/&gt;
	3) Both payoffs give him/her the same expected earnings in Stage 2. &lt;br/&gt;"
        var="Control2.5" defaultinput="" textbox="true" number="int" min="2" max="2"/>

      <question text="Assume Person B expects to click away more than 50% of the boxes in Stage 2. 
	Which of the following statements is true? &lt;br/&gt;
	Please read the following statements and choose the correct one by typing the corresponding number into the field below. &lt;br/&gt;
	1) The performance-based payoff gives him/her higher expected earnings in Stage 2. &lt;br/&gt;
	2) The random payoff gives him/her higher expected earnings in Stage 2. &lt;br/&gt;
	3) Both payoffs give him/her the same expected earnings in Stage 2. &lt;br/&gt;"
	var="Control2.6" defaultinput="" textbox="true" number="int" min="1" max="1"/>


      <question text="Imagine Person B expects to click away 30% of the boxes. Does he receive higher expected earnings from Stage 2 if
	you choose a 25% or a 75% likelihood of you receiving a performance-based payoff? &lt;br/&gt;
        Please read the following statements and choose the correct one by typing the corresponding number into the field below. &lt;br/&gt;
        1) 75%. &lt;br/&gt;
        2) Both yield the same expected payoff. &lt;br/&gt;
        3) 25%. &lt;br/&gt;"
        var="Control2.7" defaultinput="" textbox="true" number="int" min="3" max="3"/>


      <question text="Imagine Person B expects to click away 60% of the boxes. Does he receive higher expected earnings from Stage 2 if
	you choose a 25% or a 75% likelihood of you receiving a performance-based payoff? &lt;br/&gt;
        Please read the following statements and choose the correct one by typing the corresponding number into the field below. &lt;br/&gt;
        1) 75%. &lt;br/&gt;
        2) Both yield the same expected payoff. &lt;br/&gt;
        3) 25%. &lt;br/&gt;"
        var="Control2.8" defaultinput="" textbox="true" number="int" min="1" max="1"/>

    </screen>


        
<!-- Role 2/A chooses Information Technology -->
    <screen condition="#[ Self.Role == 1 ]#">
        <message text="&lt;b&gt; Stage 2: Waiting for Person A &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;
            Remember, your earnings in Stage 2 will depend on your decisions, but also depend on those of Person A that you are paired with."/>
        <message text="Person A will now be informed about your performance in Stage 1 and will choose between her 
		       options a) and b): &lt;br/&gt;
		       
		       &lt;ol type=&quot;a&quot;&gt;
		       &lt;li&gt; with a 75%  chance your earnings in stage 2 will be performance-based and with a 25% 
		       chance your earnings will be random. &lt;/li&gt;
		       &lt;li&gt; with a 25% chance your earnings in stage 2 will be performance-based and with a 75% 
		       chance your earnings will be random. &lt;/li&gt;
		       &lt;/ol&gt; 

	    That means, Person A chooses the likelihood with which you will receive a performance-based payment in 
	    Stage 2. On the next page you will be informed about Person A’s choice. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 
            Please press 'Next' and wait for Person A to make his  choice."/>
    </screen>
    
    <screen condition="#[ Self.Role == 2 ]#">
        <question text="&lt;b&gt; Stage 2: Choosing the likelihood &lt;b/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;/br&gt;
			
            On this page you will be informed about the other Person's performance in Stage 1. After that, you have 
	    to choose the likelihood with which your Person B receives a performance-based payment in Stage 2. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 
            
            &lt;b/&gt; Person B's Performance in Stage 1: &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt;
            Person B clicked away #[ Group[1].Answers['score2'] ]#% of the boxes during the box-clicking task in the first stage. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; 
            
            &lt;b/&gt; Your Choice: &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt;
            You have to choose the likelihood with which Person B receives a performance-based payoff:&lt;br/&gt;
				
	    You can choose either 25 or 75. If you choose, for instance, 25 there is a 25% chance that Person B 
	    receives a performance-based payment. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        
            Remember your costs associated with this choice are 20 DKK for the low likelihood of 25% and 30 for the 
	    high likelihood of 75%. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;        
                
            Please indicate your choice between the two likelihoods by clicking the corresponding box and press 'Next' to proceed. &lt;br/&gt;"
        
            var="PersonAProb">
            <option text="25"/>
            <option text="75"/>
        </question>
    </screen>


    <!-- Role 1/B is informed about the IT choice -->
    <screen wait="true" condition="#[ Self.Role == 1 ]#">
      <message text="
	&lt;b&gt; Stage 2: Person A's decision &lt;b/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;/br&gt;
	Person A chose a likelihood of &lt;b/&gt; #[Group[2].Answers['PersonAProb']]#% &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
				
	As a consequence, you receive a performance-based payment in Stage 2 with a likelihood of &lt;b/&gt; #[Group[2].Answers['PersonAProb']]#% &lt;/b&gt;
	and you will receive a random payment with a likelihood of #[ 100 - float(Group[2].Answers['PersonAProb']) ]#%&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
               
	Remember, a performance-based payment means that the likelihood with which you earn 225 DKK is given by the percentage of boxes you clicked away.
	A random payment simply means that you have a 50% chance to earn 75 DKK and a 50% chance to earn 225 DKK."/>
      <message text="You can choose your workload on the next page. Press 'Next' when you are ready."/>
    </screen>

    <screen condition="#[ Self.Role == 2 ]#">
      <message text="&lt;b&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Stage 2: Waiting for Person B &lt;b/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;/br&gt;
	Person B will now decide on how many screens he intends to work.
        He will then start working on the task. 
        Please press 'Next' and wait for Person B to finish the work task. This may take a few minutes."/>
    </screen>


    <!-- Role 1/B chooses amount of Screens -->
    <screen wait="false" condition="#[ Self.Role == 1 ]#">
      <question text="&lt;b/&gt; Stage 2: Choose your workload &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;
        Please indicate on how many screens you intend to work in the subsequent box-clicking task. You can choose any
	number between 1 and 25 (number of Screens!) &lt;br/&gt;"
      var="screenChoice" defaultinput="" textbox="true" number="int" min="1" max="10" />
          
      <message text="On the next page the work task will start. Press 'Next' when you are ready."/>

    </screen>
   
    
    
<!-- Role 1/B starts the box task -->
    <screen condition="#[ Self.Role == 1 ]#" noreload="true">
      <question var="boxdata" javascript="TaskBrowse.js" javascriptinput=""/>
      <question var="score" javascriptinput="1"/>
      <question var="browse" javascriptinput="#[ Self.Answers['screenChoice'] ]#"/> <!-- #[ Self.Answers['screenChoice'] ]# -->
    </screen>
    
    
<!-- Calculate Payment for Role 1/B-->
    <!-- Show role 1's true performance to role 2, if his observe effort is higher than a randomly drawn number (rand1). Else show a randomly drawn number (rand2) -->
    <screen wait="true" condition="#[ Self.Role == 1 ]#">

      <onload var="Rand1" val="#[Rand.Int(0,100)]#" />
      <onload var="Rand2" val="#[Rand.Int(0,100)]#" />
      <onload var="Rand3" val="#[Rand.Int(0,100)]#" />
      <onload var="Rand4" val="#[Rand.Int(0,100)]#" />
      <onload var="Rand5" val="#[Rand.Int(0,100)]#" />
      

      <onload var="StageB"    val="#[1  if float(Group[1].Answers['Rand1']) >= 50 else 2]#" />
      <onload var="PayB1"     val="#[150 if float(Group[1].Answers['Rand2']) >= float(Group[1].Answers['score2']) else 225]#" />
      <onload var="PayB2E"    val="#[150 if float(Group[1].Answers['Rand3']) >= float(Group[1].Answers['score']) else 225]#" />
      <onload var="PayB2R"    val="#[150 if float(Group[1].Answers['Rand4']) >= 50 else 225]#" />
      <onload var="Mechanism" val="#[0  if float(Group[1].Answers['Rand5']) >= float(Group[2].Answers['PersonAProb']) else 1]#" />

      <message text="&lt;b/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Results: Stage 2&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            Your performance: You clicked away #[ Self.Answers['score'] ]#% of the boxes during the box-clicking task.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
            On the next page we will inform you about the stage that will be paid out and your earnings in that stage." />
      <message text="Please press 'Next' to continue." />      
    </screen>

    <screen wait="true" condition="#[ Self.Role == 1 ]#">
      
      <message text="
            The computer is calculating your payoff right now. This may take a few seconds." />
      <message text="Please press 'Next' to continue." /> 
      
      <onload var="PayB2"     val="#[Group[1].Answers['PayB2E'] if float(Group[1].Answers['Mechanism']) >= 1 else Group[1].Answers['PayB2R']]#" />
      <onload var="PaymentB"  val="#[Group[1].Answers['PayB2'] if float(Group[1].Answers['StageB']) >= 2 else Group[1].Answers['PayB1']]#" />
    </screen>
 
    

<!-- Calculate Payment for Role 2/A-->
    <screen wait="false" condition="#[ Self.Role == 2 ]#">
      <onload var="Rand6" val="#[Rand.Int(0,100)]#" />
      <onload var="Rand7" val="#[Rand.Int(0,100)]#" />

      <onload var="CostsA" val="#[25 if float(Self.Answers['PersonAProb']) >= 75 else 20]#" />
      


      <onload var="StageA"    val="#[1 if float(Group[2].Answers['Rand6']) >= 50 else 2]#" />
      <onload var="PayA1"     val="#[150 if float(Group[2].Answers['Rand7']) >= float(Group[2].Answers['score2']) else 225]#" />
      <onload var="PayA2"     val="#[350 - float(Group[1].Answers['PaymentB']) + 0.75 * float(Group[1].Answers['score']) - float(Group[2].Answers['CostsA']) ]#" />
      <onload var ="PaymentA" val="#[float(Group[2].Answers['PayA2']) if float(Group[2].Answers['StageA']) >= 2 else float(Group[2].Answers['PayA1'])]#" />

      <message text="&lt;b/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Results: Stage 2&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            Person B's performance: Person B clicked away #[ Group[1].Answers['score'] ]#% of the boxes during the box-clicking task.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
            On the next page we will inform you about the stage that will be paid out and your earnings in that stage." />
      <message text="Please press 'Next' to continue." />
    </screen> 
    
    
<!-- Display Payoffs-->
    <screen condition="#[ Self.Role == 1 ]#">
      <message text="&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thank you!" />
      <message text="The stage which will be paid out is: Stage #[ Self.Answers['StageB'] ]#" />
      <message text="Your earnings in this experiment are: #[ Self.Answers['PaymentB'] ]# DKK" />
      <message text="Please press 'Next' to continue." />
      <onload var="payment" val="#[ Self.Answers['PaymentB'] ]#" />
    </screen>
    
    <screen condition="#[ Self.Role == 2 ]#">
      <message text="&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thank you!" />
      <message text="The stage which will be paid out is: Stage #[ Self.Answers['StageA'] ]#" />
      <message text="Your earnings in this experiment are: #[ Self.Answers['PaymentA'] ]# DKK" />
      <message text="Please press 'Next' to continue." />
      <onload var="payment" val="#[ Self.Answers['PaymentA'] ]#" />
    </screen>

		
<!-- Final Questionnaire for both Players -->
	<screen>
        <question text="&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b/&gt;Final Questionnaire&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
				
            Imagine the following situation: you are shopping in an unfamiliar city and realize you lost your way. 
			You ask a stranger for directions. The stranger offers to take you with his car to your destination. 
			The ride takes about 20 minutes and costs the stranger about 200 DKK in total. 
			The stranger does not want money for it. You carry six bottles of wine with you. 
			The cheapest bottle costs 50 DKK, the most expensive one 300 DKK. 
			You decide to give one of the bottles to the stranger as a thank-you gift. Which bottle do you give?&lt;br/&gt;"
            var="Reciprocity1">
            <option text="50 DKK worth"/>
            <option text="100 DKK worth"/>
            <option text="150 DKK worth"/>
            <option text="200 DKK worth"/>
            <option text="250 DKK worth"/>
            <option text="300 DKK worth"/>
		</question>

        <question text="How do you see yourself: If I am treated very unjustly, 
			I will take revenge at the first occasion, even if there is a cost to do so.&lt;br/&gt;"
            var="Reciprocity2">
            <option text="Completely untrue of me"/>
            <option text="Mostly untrue of me"/>
            <option text="Slightly more untrue than true"/>
            <option text="Slightly more true than untrue"/>
            <option text="Mostly true of me"/>
            <option text="Describes me perfectly"/>
        </question>

        <question text="How do you see yourself: When someone does me a favor I am willing to return it.&lt;br/&gt;"
            var="Reciprocity3">
            <option text="Completely untrue of me"/>
            <option text="Mostly untrue of me"/>
            <option text="Slightly more untrue than true"/>
            <option text="Slightly more true than untrue"/>
            <option text="Mostly true of me"/>
            <option text="Describes me perfectly"/>
        </question>

		    <question text="How do you see yourself: I assume that people have only the best intentions.&lt;br/&gt;"
            var="Reciprocity4">
            <option text="Completely untrue of me"/>
            <option text="Mostly untrue of me"/>
            <option text="Slightly more untrue than true"/>
            <option text="Slightly more true than untrue"/>
            <option text="Mostly true of me"/>
            <option text="Describes me perfectly"/>
        </question>

        <message text="Please press 'Next' to finish the experiment." />
    </screen>

<!-- Endscreen for both Players -->
    <screen endscreen="true">
      <message text="&lt;b&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thank you for participating in this experiment!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 
      Please remain seated until you are called to the payment room."/>
    </screen>
    
  </screens>
  
</root>
